提取她的血液样本
Take a sample of her blood.
- 然后把尸体扔掉 - 是，长官
- and then get rid of that. - Yes, sir.
《生化危机：灭绝》
安布雷拉公司认为他们已经控制住了病毒的传播
The Umbrella Corporation thought they'd contained the infection.
其实，他们错的
Well, they were wrong.
从Raccoon城市开始
Raccoon City was just the beginning.
几个星期后，T型病毒感染了整个美国
Within weeks, the T-virus had consumed the United States.
几个月后，全球都被感染了
Within months, the world.
病毒不仅吞噬了人类的生命
The virus didn't just wipe out human life.
河流和湖泊干涸了 森林变成了沙漠
Lakes and rivers dried up, forests became deserts.
所有的陆地都被
and whole continents were reduced to.
侵蚀为贫瘠的荒野
nothing more than barren wastelands.
可以确定的是，地球将慢慢的衰退，然后消亡
Slowly but surely, the Earth began to wither and die.
为数不多的幸存者都 要去适应去漂泊的生活
What few survivors there were learned to keep on the move.
我们避开大城市
We avoided major cities.
如果我们在一个地方呆时间太长，就会被它们发现
If we stopped anyplace too long, they would be drawn to us.
先是来几个，随后会越来越多
Only a few at first, but then more and more.
一群僵尸组成的不死军团
A never-ending army of undead.
作为幸存者的我们
For those of us left.
似乎只有不停的游走
staying on the road.
才能继存活下去
seemed the only way to stay alive.
（盐湖城市）
这里是KLKB 我们有7个人
This is KLKB. We have seven people here.
需要紧急医治
in need of urgent medical attention.
我们需要帮助，这里是KLKB 有人听到吗 ？
We need help. This is KLKB. Can anyone hear us?
有人来救我们吗？求求你们了
Can anyone help us? Please?
我的孩子
My baby.
求求你
Please.
求求你救救我的孩子
Please help my baby.
你个婊子
You bitch.
你把我的孩子摔倒地上了
You dropped my baby.
我们被包围了，我们需要帮忙 有人听到吗？
We're surrounded. We need help. Can anyone hear us?
- 有人来救我们吗？求求你们了 - 每次都管用啊，老妈
- Can anyone help us? Please. - Works every time, Mama.
让我们来看看
Let's see.
- 她还带了些什么东西 - 是啊
- what else she's packing. - Yeah.
你这里面藏的是什么，傻妞？
What you got down there, fishy?
我要是你的话就不会那么做
I wouldn't do that.
闭嘴！
Shut your mouth!
- 冷静点！ - 让这个婊子见识见识
- Relax! - Just show the bitch.
埃迪！埃迪！埃迪！
Eddie! Eddie! Eddie!
天呐！他死了！
Jesus Christ! He's dead!
你以为你很厉害，是吧？
Think you're pretty smart, huh?
走着瞧
Well, you'll see.
接着，婊子 我希望你死的别太快了！
There you go, bitch. I wouldn't want it to be over too fast!
把笼子打开！
Open the cage!
放它们出去
Let them loose.
快闪开！
Get up now!
喷的可真多啊，看到没？
That was a juicy one, huh?
嘿，卡洛斯，我是克莱尔
Hey, Carlos, this is Claire.
- 你有烟吗？ - 没有
- You got any smokes? - No.
鬼才信呢
Like I'm supposed to believe that.
克莱尔，我会骗你吗？
Claire, would I lie to you?
- L.J。- 克莱尔 雷德菲尔德，有什么我能帮忙吗？
- L.J. - Claire Redfield, how can I help you?
- 有烟吗？ - 这可帮不了你
- Got any smokes? - No can do.
问问你的搭档有吗？
How about alternate?
很抱歉，我们都没有了
Sorry to say we're out of that too.
你们也太打击我了，奥托有吗？
You gotta be shitting me. Otto?
不好意思，伙计。在盐湖那我抽掉了最后一根
Sorry, campers. Smoked the last of it back in Salt Lake.
该死的
Damn.
- 嘿，伙计们 - 该死的
- Yeah, people - Damn it.
这可真的是世界末日了
it really is the end of the world.
- 还有谁要发言？ - 巴黎的情况
- Anyone else? - Paris facility.
食品供应下降了50%
Food supplies down to 50 percent.
6个人被感染 生化人数量持续增加中
Six casualties. Biohazard numbers increasing.
伦敦的情况
London facility.
食品供应下降了28% 有17人被感染
Food supplies down to 28 percent. Seventeen casualties.
生化人数量持续增加中
Biohazard numbers increasing.
先生们
Gentlemen.
艾萨克斯博士
Dr. Isaacs.
有科学家参与这个会议真是太好了
How good of the science division to join us.
韦斯克主席，我最近很忙
Chairman Wesker. I've been busy.
在生化危机问题上 科学家有什么建议？
On the subject of the biohazard, what is the science division's report?
是这样，我们现在得到这样一个结论 它们不需要任何食物来维持生命
Well, we now know conclusively that they have no real need for sustenance.
他们渴望吃肉 但却不是必须的
They hunger for flesh but do not require it.
我的研究表明 它们大约会存活10年左右
My research indicates they could remain active for decades.
也就是说我们要被困在地下10年？
We're to be trapped underground for decades?
艾莉丝项目有什么进展？
What news of Project Alice?
利用她血液中的抗体
Using antibodies from her blood.
我配制了一种血清 不仅可以击溃T型病毒
I will develop a serum that will not just combat the effects of the T-virus.
而且还可以进化它
but potentially reverse it.
从而使那些不生不死的家伙们重新获得一点智力
giving back these creatures a measure of their intelligence.
一点记忆能力，同时还能控制他们吃肉的欲望
their memories, thus curbing their hunger for flesh.
你有信心驯化它们？
You're confident you can domesticate them?
从本质上说，它们是动物
They're animals, essentially.
如果我们能够除掉它们的某些本性，我们可以驯服它们
We can train them, if we can take away their baser instincts.
它们不可能在变回人类了
They'll never be human.
不过他们可以成为一种温顺的劳动力
but would provide the basis for a docile workforce.
我们可以重新回到地面上去
We can return to the surface.
已经试验了好几个月了 可你却仍没什么进展
After months of experiments, you have nothing to show.
- 我们在这里已经待腻了 - 没有了原版的艾莉丝
- We are left to rot underground. - Without the original Project Alice.
进展变得缓慢了
progress has been difficult.
现在我不得不去克隆她 不断的利用她的克隆体
I've been forced to replicate her using cloned genetic models.
这是件很艰苦的事 而结果，是不确定的
It's laborious. The results, unpredictable.
艾莉丝计划和驯化项目拥有最高优先权
Project Alice and the subject of domestication is of the highest priority.
你要全力投入到这两个项目上 不要管其他的研究了
You will concentrate on this to the exclusion of all other research.
我们希望一周后会又新的进展
We expect an updated report in a week.
太急于求成不会得到很好的效果
Simply demanding results will not guarantee them.
那或许我们应该再找个负责人了
Then perhaps we should place someone else in charge.
一个可以满足我们需要的人
Someone who can give us the reassurances we require.
继续你的研究吧，博士
Continue with your research, doctor.
那仍然是你负责的研究
while it still is your research.
会议到此为止
This meeting is adjourned.
抱歉，史蒂维
Sorry about this, Stevie.
这里是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德车队 我们在搜寻生还者
This is Claire Redfield's convoy, broadcasting for any survivors.
有生还者吗？
Is anybody out there?
我们在搜寻生还者 有人在吗？
Broadcasting for any survivors. Is anybody out there?
这里是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德车队 我们在搜寻生还者
This is Claire Redfield's convoy, broadcasting for any survivors.
有生还者吗？
Is anybody out there?
这里是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德车队 目前已到达沙漠之迹旅馆
This is Claire Redfield's convoy. Location, the Desert Trail Motel.
我们在搜寻生还者 里面有人吗？
Broadcasting for any survivors. ls there anybody in there?
继续通信，麦基
Keep trying, Mikey.
里面有生还者吗？
ls there anyone alive in there?
请回答
Please respond.
- 看起来挺安静的 - 是啊，一直不都是这样的吗？
- Seems quiet. - Yeah, don't they always?
里面有生还者吗？ 请回答
Is there anyone alive in there? Please respond.
克莱尔，里面好像没人，我们要进去吗？
Claire. Looks clear. Shall we go in?
你们自己决定，伙计们
It's your call, boys.
- 来吧，我们上 - 我们去搜搜
- Come on. Let's go. - Let's do it.
我要找个房间
I'm gonna get me a room.
睡在水床上，来个按摩式浴缸
I'll take a waterbed, a Jacuzzi.
然后再弄本色情书刊
and I'm gonna rent me a porno.
怎么了？你们俩还好吗？
What happened? You two okay?
很好，这里安全了
Yeah. It's all clear.
有人需要我帮忙吗？
Somebody need my help?
这没什么了，不过要是你坚持的话
It's nothing. But if you insist.
很好，坐回去，放松点
That's right. So sit back and relax.
大家解散，都去找点我们需要的东西 汽油、食物、弹药，你们知道我们需要什么
Spread out. Look for anything of use. Gas, food, ammo. You know the drill.
你看起来像是打了场硬仗，是吧？
You like playing rough, huh?
- 哦，我还遇到过比这糟的呢 - 看得出来
- Oh, I've had worse. - I'm sure.
不过你总是对我这么好啊，贝蒂
But you've always been gentle with me, Betty.
哦，天呐，受不了你们了
Oh, God. I'm leaving.
那该怎么说呢 你今晚到我那儿吃晚饭？
So, what do we say, dinner at my place tonight?
哦，我会去的
Oh, I'm there.
嘿，贝蒂！过来一下！
Hey, Betty! Over here!
太惊人了 他知道这是什么
This is amazing. He knows what it is.
相机
Camera.
你来试试
You try.
站好
Stand your ground.
- 天呐 - 太不可思议了
- My God. - Unbelievable.
他有了记忆和推理能力
He has memory and reasoning skills.
这真是奇迹啊，血浆起作用了，你真的驯化了他们
This is incredible. The serum works. You've domesticated them.
你成功了，恭喜啊
You've done it. Congratulations.
别这样，博士！ 求你了，别这样！
No, doctor! Please. No!
不，别这样，博士 求你了，别这样！
No, no, doctor. Please, no!
猪肉豆子罐头，我再给你个小桃子罐头
Pork and beans. I'll get some peaches for the little one there.
下一个
There you go.
- 这是芦笋罐头 - 谢谢
- It's asparagus. - Thanks.
对于你吗
For you.
猫粮
cat food.
开个玩笑了，那是猪肉豆子罐头
Just kidding. It's pork and beans.
- 嘿 - 这是什么，猜猜？
- Hey. - What's this, huh?
- 汤，奶油蘑菇汤罐头 - 扯淡
- Soup. Cream of mushroom. - Bullshit.
- 我猜还是猪肉豆子罐头 - 谢谢，伙计
- I think that's pork and beans too. - Thanks, man.
- 你还真猜对了 - 芦笋罐头
- I'll be damned. - Asparagus.
- 你是怎么猜出来的？ - 这只是我的一点小本事
- How do you do that? - Just one of my skills.
很可惜，只是濒临死亡的艺术
It's a dying art, unfortunately.
这是最后一罐了
This is the last of it.
- 我猜是一种水果的罐头 - 谢谢你，奥托
- I think it's some kind of fruit. - Thanks, Otto.
很抱歉我们只有这些了
Sorry, that's all we have.
水果，你想要水果罐头吗？
Fruit. You want some fruit?
- 你查看过加油站了吗？ - 看过了，不过一点油都没有
- Did you check out the gas station? - Yep, it's bone-dry.
那这里情况怎么样？
Well, how we looking here?
克莱尔，如果铁锈能当燃料的话
Well, Claire, if we can run these trucks on rust.
看起来还蛮酷的
we're looking pretty good.
好吧
All right.
嘿，宝贝儿
Hey, sweetheart.
监视墙建起来了吗？
Perimeter up yet?
快弄好了
It's almost done.
- 谁在外围？ - 奧利維拉
- Who's out there? - Olivera.
- 嘿，卡洛斯 - 克莱尔
- Hey, Carlos. - Claire.
抽烟都把你抽垮了 加把劲，老家伙
All that smoking is slowing you down. Get your ass in gear, old man.
赶紧把监视墙布置好
I want my perimeter up.
最后一个监视器已经到位了
Last sentinel in place.
监视墙可以运行了 所有的传感器都运转正常
Perimeter's up and running. All motion sensors online.
摄影机工作完全正常
Cameras 100 percent.
炸豆泥，水果沙拉
Refried beans. Fruit salad.
哦，都是我最爱吃的
Oh, my favorite.
沙尘暴要来了！
Storm's coming!
大家把东西收拾起来都到车里面去
Let's start packing it up and move it inside.
- 来吧，孩子们，上车！ - 快点！
- Come on, kids, let's go! - Hurry up!
到车里面去，把火扑灭
Get back in the bus. Put this fire out.
这里是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德车队 已到达沙漠之迹旅馆
This is Claire Redfield's convoy. Location, the Desert Trail Motel.
北纬35度，西经114度 搜寻生还者
Lat. 35, long. 114. Calling any survivors.
这里是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德车队 已到达沙漠之迹旅馆
This is Claire Redfield's convoy. Location, the Desert Trail Motel.
北纬35度，西经114度 搜寻生还者
Lat. 35, long. 114. Calling any survivors.
激活第87号
Activate Number 87.
该死的
Shit.
- 艾萨克斯博士 - 什么事？
- Dr. Isaacs. - What is it?
我的传感器检测到一个意念行为高峰信号
My sensors have detected a peak in psionic activity.
α和β射线都检测到了
Both alpha and beta wave.
是87号发出的吗？
From Number 87?
不是，那个意念行为不是从任何克隆体发出的
No, the activity's not from one of the clones.
它发生在复合实验室外
lt occurred outside the complex.
- 不可能 - 我的传感器精确的检测到了
- That's not possible. - My sensors were quite clear.
15分钟前检测到能量巨大意念行为
Massive psionic activity was detected 15 minutes ago.
能量中心位于沙漠地带
centered on a desert location.
- 克莱尔！ - 怎么了？
- Claire! - What?
这是他妈怎么回事儿？
What the hell?
哦，天呐
Oh, God.
- 卡洛斯 - 我看到了
- Carlos. - I see them.
大家都呆在卡车里别动
Everybody stay in your trucks.
怎么回事儿？
What's going on?
大家都呆在卡车里别动
Everyone just stay in your trucks.
把窗户关上，保持安静
Roll up the windows and keep quiet.
好了，把窗户关上
Okay, close the windows up.
它们的眼睛怎么了？
What's wrong with their eyes?
它们吃了被感染了的肉
They've been feeding on infected flesh.
- 把车启动起来，我们得赶紧离开这儿 - 这可是个不错的主意
- Fire it up. Let's get out of here. - That's a hell of an idea.
子弹上膛
Lock and load.
- 我们被卡住了 - 哦，别这样啊，我们得离开这儿
- We're stuck! - Hell, no, let's get out of here.
我们得到那辆公交车上去，来吧
Let's head for the bus, come on.
来吧！快！快！
Come on! Go! Go!
快点，上来！ 快点，快点，快点
Come on, get in! Come on, come on, come on.
克莱尔！
Claire!
该死的
Damn it.
麦基，卡洛斯 我们得回公交车那儿去
Mikey, Carlos, we have to evac the bus.
收到
You got it.
挺住！
Hold it!
- 快点，快走！ - 别停下来！
- Come on, move! - Keep moving!
快啊！快！快！快！快点！
Come on! Go! Go! Go! Come on!
- 贝蒂！ - 快走！别管我！
- Betty! - Go! Just go!
快离开这儿，贝蒂！快走！
Get out of here, Betty! Go!
- 快！快！快！ - 开车！
- Move! Move! Move! - Go!
- 贝蒂！贝蒂！ - LJ，快点！
- Betty! Betty! - L.J., hurry up!
跟我来！
Come with me!
快！快！贝蒂！贝蒂！
Come on! Come on! Betty! Betty!
不！
No!
贝蒂！
Betty!
快走！快开车！快！
Go! Go! Go!
艾萨克斯博士
Dr. Isaacs.
α和β射线又检测到了一个峰值
Another spike in alpha and beta waves detected.
有百分之45的可能这是由艾莉丝发出的
Forty-five percent probability that this is Project Alice.
三角定位，找到她的位置
Triangulate. Find her location.
太惊人了
lmpressive.
如果是她的话，她的进化可真特别啊
lf it is her, her development is extraordinary.
从她逃离底特律实验基地开始
Her powers would appear to have grown at a geometric rate.
她的能量会以几何形式增长
since her escape from the Detroit facility.
在24小时之内 你未经允许去过地表面10次
You've made 10 trips to the surface in the past 24 hours. All unauthorized.
每次离开实验基地，尤其是去采集样品，都会使我的人冒生命危险
Any trip to the surface, especially to gather specimens, puts my men at risk.
你为什么要突然出去这么多次？
Why do you need so many all of a sudden?
艾萨克斯！
Isaacs!
我已经加强了研究力度
My research has intensified.
别担心，它们被困的很牢
Don't worry. They're perfectly secure.
你不是应该驯化它们的吗？
You're supposed to be domesticating them.
有时候攻击力也是有用的
Sometimes aggression has its uses.
那你需要这些家伙干什么？
What could you possibly need these things for?
艾萨克斯博士
Dr. Isaacs.
87号实验品已经到达了实验的最后阶段
Specimen 87 has reached the final stage of the test grid.
很好，把监视画面调到屏幕上
Perfect. Put her on the screen.
好姑娘
Good girl.
韦斯克主席知道这些吗？
ls Chairman Wesker even aware of this?
他知道他该知道的事儿
He knows what he needs to know.
你做的也太过分了
You've overstepped your mark.
我的研究将改变现在的一切
My research will change the face of everything.
如果你要选择一个阵营的话
If you pick a side.
一定要选择一个正确的
be sure it's the right one.
嗨
Hi.
嘿
Hey.
这是你的？
This belong to you?
我昨晚给你戴上的
I gave it to you last night.
它会带给你好运的
For luck.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
凯马特
K-Mart.
那是他们找到我的地方
It's where they found me.
克莱尔和其他人
Claire and the other.
几年前的事儿了
A few years back.
你还有其他名字吗？
Do you have another name?
一直都不喜欢那个名字
Never liked it.
我认识的每个人都死去了
Everyone I knew was dead.
似乎需要做些改变的时候到了
so seemed like time for a change.
谁想说点什么吗？
Anyone want to say something?
艾莉丝，这是克莱尔 雷德菲尔德
Alice, this is Claire Redfield.
她是这个车队的组织者
She's the one who put this convoy together.
谢谢你出手帮忙
Thank you so much for your help.
克莱尔！
Claire!
失陪一下，有点事儿我得处理一下
Excuse me. I have things I have to attend to.
在过去的6个月里 她损失了一半的车队
ln the last six months, she lost half of the convoy.
过不了多久，我们会有更多的人死去
Pretty soon there'll be more of us dead than alive.
艾莉丝，你怎么了？
Alice, what happened to you?
在底特律之后你为什么走了？
Why did you leave after Detroit?
我没得选择 他们在利用我
I didn't have a choice. They were using me.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
他们一直在跟踪我
They were tracking me.
我不能靠近你们中的任何一个人
I couldn't be around you. Any of you.
- 我不能让你们都被杀掉 - 所以你离开了
- I would've gotten you all killed. - That's why you disappeared?
我破译了密码进入了他们的系统
Broke into an Umbrella facility and hacked into their computers.
下载了卫星的运行轨道信息
downloaded the satellite trajectories.
避开了跟踪
and stayed off the grid.
在世界灭亡后
And after the world ended?
为什么独自留在那儿？
Why stay out there alone?
如果我离开了，大家会更安全
It's just safer if I'm not around people.
那为什么回来？
Why'd you come back?
该死
Damn!
几点了？
What time is it?
蔡斯，现在几点了？
Chase, what time is it?
嗯，卡洛斯，十二点十四分 有什么想去的地方吗？
Well, Carlos, it is 12:14. Why? You got somewhere you gotta be?
我想我刚刚又犯妄想症了
Guess I'm just being paranoid.
欢迎回家
Welcome home.
有空吗？
Got a minute?
当然
Yeah.
每个人都很感激你的帮助
Everyone is grateful for you helping us out.
但是我又能呆多久呢？
But how long am I gonna stay?
别误会
Don't get me wrong.
我们真的很感动
We really are grateful.
他们都在谈论你做过的事，他们很害怕
They're all talking about what you did. And they're scared.
我没有责怪他们
I don't blame them.
人们习惯了我和死亡同行
People have a habit of dying around me.
不只是你
Not just you.
你确定是她
You're positive it's her?
62%符合，不可能让她跑掉
Sixty-two percent. Too great a chance to pass up.
如果真是艾莉丝 那么她已经躲避卫星追踪很多年了
lf it is Project Alice, she's been evading the satellite grid for years.
我已经改道发送了剩下的卫星
I've re-routed the remaining satellites.
一切在我们的控制之中，她不会觉察到我们的监控
We can reacquire the subject. She'll be unaware of surveillance.
我能在一个小时内组织一支特攻队
I can have a strike team ready within the hour.
不，我们先要确定身份
No. We'll establish a positive identification first.
百分百的确定
One hundred percent.
和她一起的人很有名
The group she's with include known associates.
原版的艾莉丝对我的研究
The original Project Alice is vital to my research.
和整个驯化项目至关重要 她的血
to the whole process of domestication. Her blood.
她的基因结构是成功的关键
her genetic structure, is the key.
她在外面时间越长 我们失去她的可能就越大
The longer she's out there, the greater chance we lose her.
- 我不能冒险 - 决定权不在你手里
- I can't risk that. - That decision isn't yours to make.
在下次会议委员会讨论前 你不能擅自行动
Take no action until this matter has been discussed by the committee.
还有一点，博士
at the next scheduled meeting. And, doctor.
这是个命令
That's an order.
这是几个月来最接近有生命迹象的信号
These transmissions are the best indication of life we've seen in months.
- 阿拉斯加？ - 我们应该去查看一下
- Alaska? - We have to check it out.
我们不能忽视它
We can't just ignore it.
你们知道路上会发生什么事情吗？
Any idea what kind of journey that would be?
- 知道，会很漫长 - 最后呢？
- Yeah. A long one. - And at the end of it, what?
你们甚至不能保证那有活着的人
You have no guarantee there's even anyone alive up there.
- 传送的信号显示 - 那是六个月前的
- These transmissions say that - They're dated six months ago.
我们回复了多少无线信号？
How many radio broadcasts have we responded to?
多少次我们晚到一步？
How many times have we got there too late?
信号显示那儿没有被污染
The transmissions say that there's no infection up there.
那儿与世隔绝
It's isolated.
是安全的
Safe.
这个车队的人把他们的生命交给我
This convoy trusts me with their lives.
他们不需要白日梦
These people don't need pipe dreams.
也许那正是他们需要的
Maybe that's exactly what they need.
克莱尔，看看他们
Look at them, Claire.
六个月前我们有50个人 然后40，现在不过30
Six months ago, there were 50 of us, then 40, now there's less than 30.
他们开始放弃了
They're starting to give up.
他们需要希望
They need some kind of hope.
我们得做个抉择
We have a decision to make.
因为它的重要性 所以我无法代大家决定
And it's too big, it's too important for me to make for you.
那里也许会有生还者
There's a chance there are survivors.
哪儿？
Where?
在阿拉斯加
ln Alaska.
也许
There is a chance.
污染没有扩散的那么远
that the infection hasn't reached that far.
但是我们不确定
But we don't know for sure.
所以这只是一个建议
So we have a choice.
我们可以继续留在这里
We stay as we are.
或者去阿拉斯加碰碰运气
or we try for Alaska.
支持去阿拉斯加的
For Alaska.
阿拉斯加
Alaska.
我希望你是对的
I hope you're right.
上帝
God.
食物都吃完了 油也快没了
The food's virtually gone and the truck's running on empty.
我弄到了半桶油，给你
I've got half a tank of gas. That's it.
- 蔡斯 - 去他的，我甚至连个空油桶都没有
- Chase? - Shit, I don't even have empty.
我的够走一百英里的，上好的油
I got enough for a hundred miles, tops.
如果我们要去的话 就必须补给一下了
lf we're gonna make this trip, we'll need to resupply.
是的
Yep.
只有这些选择了
These are our options.
最近最安全的选择就是去那儿了
The nearest, safest bet is right there.
那边是空的，我已经试过了
No, it's empty. I tried that.
那么，好的，也许
Then, well, maybe.
- 我们可以试试这个 - 拉斯维加斯
- We could try this - Vegas.
那儿是唯一我确信可以弄到补给的地方了
It's the only place we're sure to find gas and supplies.
可是拉斯维加斯很危险
There's a reason for that. Vegas is too dangerous.
和那些杂种一起爬行
It's crawling with them sons of bitches.
过去的六个月 我们已经去过了每一个小镇
We've drained every small town dry over the last six months.
我们必须去一个大点儿的城市
We have to hit a big city.
她是对的
She's right.
拉斯维加斯是我们唯一能去的地方了
Vegas, it's our only bet.
我们将做一个身份识别
We'll establish a positive identification.
百分之一百的
One hundred percent.
不要轻举妄动 等着委员会来讨论这件事情
Take no action until this matter has been discussed by the committee.
博士
Doctor.
这是命令
That's an order.
委员会签署了立即行动令
The committee authorizes immediate action.
给车辆和人员放行
Release of vehicles and personnel.
由艾萨克斯博士签署
under command of Dr. Isaacs.
这是命令
That's an order.
喂，你还好吗？
Hey. You all right?
嗯，还行
Yeah, I'm fine.
那些猪肉和豆类，那些致命的玩意 我不知道你们是怎么做到的？
Them pork and beans, they lethal. I don't see how you cowboys do it.
多年的训练
Years of practice.
（欢迎来到拉斯维加斯）
噢，上帝
Oh, my God.
发生什么了？
What happened to it?
沙漠又回来了
The desert must have taken it back.
5年了
Five years.
没有人去阻止沙化过程
No one to keep the sand back.
是空的
It's empty.
没有生物
No undead.
什么也没有
Nothing.
那些鸟搜遍了这个城市的每一个街区
Those birds must have moved through the city block by block.
清洗了一切
Picked it clean.
我没有看见有卡车停下
I don't see any truck stops.
他们去哪儿了？
Where are they?
那儿
There.
瓦利特停在了卡西诺赌场上面
Valet parking at the casino up ahead.
那儿有汽油
There's gas pumps in there.
你怎么知道的？
Now, how do you know that?
那天我在这儿输了两千块
I dropped two G's back in the day here.
你输了两千美金？
You lost $2000?
该死
Damn it.
清理一下
Spread them out!
我们得把它们搬走
We're gonna have to move it.
好的，蔡斯，帮我看着点
All right, Chase, I need a lookout!
那上面
Up there.
好极了
Great.
带一支大口径步枪到艾菲尔铁塔那儿去
Climb the Eiffel Tower with a high-powered rifle.
几年以前这是会引起骚动的
A few years ago, that would've caused a stir.
好了，暂时享受一下
Well, let the good times roll.
先把这个搞定
Let's get this done.
离开这个鬼地方 麦基，准备好绞盘
Get the hell out of here. Mikey, get the winch.
- 好的 - 卡洛斯
- Yeah. - Carlos.
等等
Wait.
回去
Get back!
- 卡洛斯，掩护我 - 上
- Carlos, cover me! - Go!
快走
Move!
到后边去，冷静 走，快，快去
Just get to the back and stay quiet. Go! Now! Go!
趴下
Get down!
她的确很棒
She really is magnificent.
等她一死 你一定迅速行动
When she's dead, make sure you move in fast.
我需要一份她的血样 要热的
I need a sample of her blood while it's still warm.
没问题
That won't be a problem.
- 卫星到位了吗？ - 是的，长官
- Satellite in position? - Yes, sir.
关掉她
Then shut her down.
麦基！
Mikey.
嘿
Hey!
麦基！
Mikey.
不
No!
她在抵抗
She's fighting the conditioning.
加强控制信号
Boost the control signal.
见鬼
Shit!
爬上来，把手给我
Climb! Give me your hand!
快跑
Run! Go!
Go! Run!
来吧
Let's go!
L.J.
怎么了？
What is it?
卫星出故障了
Satellite. Some kind of malfunction.
多久能恢复
How long?
还要15秒
New feed coming online in 15 seconds.
3，2，1
Online in three, two.
可以了
Now.
她到底去要去哪儿？
Where the hell is she going?
关掉她
Shut her down!
她仍在接近
She's still coming!
- 快点儿把她关掉 - 哦，见鬼
- Now! - Oh, shit.
你这个
You son of a.
返回基地
Back to base!
抗体 给我抗体
The anti-virus! Get me the anti-virus!
你为什么不开枪？
Why didn't you shoot?
因为我们不能开车去阿拉斯加我要一架完整的直升机
Because we're not driving to Alaska. I want that helicopter intact.
让我们去看看电脑 查查他们去哪儿了？
Let's go look at the computer, see where that chopper's headed.
- 他怎么样了？ - 在禁闭室里
- How is he? - Under house arrest.
照你的命令 他已经安静下来了
as you instructed. He's been quiet.
你用了多少剂量？
How much of this have you used?
她的血提升了那些生物的力量
Her blood increased the creatures' power.
还加强了影响的强度
lt also increased the strength of the infection.
我需要它
I needed it.
你不知道这对你来说意味着什么
You have no idea what this will do to you.
哦，我有个主意
Oh, I have an idea.
你的控制权失效了
You're out of control.
一切都结束了
Well, this ends here.
根据第1354号命令 由韦斯克授权
Under executive order 1345, issued by Chairman Wesker.
为了偿付在这个研究上的损失
for gross misconduct in the field.
你将被液化掉
I sentence you to summary liquidation.
液化
Liquidation?
只是死去而已
Just die.
把尸体弄走 给我关于艾莉丝的所有资料
Take the body to the surface. Bring me the stats on Program Alice.
长官
Sir!
很好，我们喜欢挑战
Good thing we like a challenge.
坚持住
Hold on.
那儿能找到抗体
They have the anti-virus in there.
坚持住
Just hold on.
已经太迟了，你知道的
It's too late, and you know it.
还有，你得想个办法进去
Besides, you need a way to get in there.
我有个主意
And I have an idea.
- 你会保证他们的安全的，对吧？ - 没问题
- You keep them safe, huh? - You got it.
过来
Come here.
卡洛斯，我
Carlos, I.
什么也别说
Save it.
你刚刚答应过我的
You just promise me one thing.
你一到下面
When you get down there.
相信我能成功的
Consider it done.
祝我能来上一口烟
Wish I had a smoke.
该死
Fuck!
马上就要死了
I'll be damned.
LJ，你个狗娘养的
L.J., you sneaky son of a bitch.
哦，妈的
Oh, hell.
快
Come on.
快把孩子们都带走
Get the kids out quickly!
快
Go!
- 快跑 - 好的
- Run! Run! Hurry up! - Okay.
快，快，快
Go! Go! Go!
带他走
Take him!
你不打算一起走？
You're not coming?
照顾好其他人
Take care of the others.
很抱歉 我不是有意要吓到你的
I'm sorry. I didn't mean to startle you.
- 我是人工智能人 - 我知道你是谁
- I am the artificial intelligence - I know what you are.
我认识你姐姐
I knew your sister.
她是个嗜血狂
She was a homicidal bitch.
我姐姐的程序只会照逻辑行事
My sister computer was merely following the most logical path.
保护人类的生命
for the preservation of human life.
对，杀了一些，救了许多
Yeah. Kill a few, save a lot.
那么这儿到底发生了什么？
So, what happened here?
艾萨克斯博士被咬了 回来的时候已经受感染了
Dr. Isaacs returned in an infected state. He was bitten by a creature.
那些生物已经用一种新的血清处理过了
that had been treated with a newly developed serum.
从你的血液里提取的血清
A serum derived from your blood.
结果引起了巨大的变化
The resulting infection has caused massive mutation.
我的血液？
My blood?
你的血液已经和T病毒绑定了
Your blood has bonded with the T-virus.
艾萨克斯博士正确的推断出
Dr. Isaacs correctly deduced.
它可以用来摧毁那些变异生物
that it could be used to destroy the biohazard for good.
你是说我的血可以拯救这一切
You mean my blood is the cure for all this?
是的
Correct.
那你为什么帮我？
So why are you helping me?
你的血液是纯净的 这个设备有
Your blood is pure, and this facility contains.
所有你需要用来合成药剂的仪器
all of the equipment you will require to synthesize a cure.
- 你是说这一切都可以结束了 - 非常正确
- You mean this could all end? - Correct.
不过还有
There is, however.
一个小问题
a small problem.
我把他困在了下面
I have him contained in the lower levels.
但是我没法困住他更久
but I cannot hold him there for much longer.
好吧，出发
All right, let's go.
艾莉丝？
Alice?
祝你好运
Good luck.
你杀不死我
You can't kill me.
我告诉过你
I've told you.
我是不死的
I can't die.
不
No.
这么久了，我一直以为你代表着未来
For so long, I thought you were the future.
结果我错了
I was wrong.
我才是真正的未来
I am the future.
不
No.
你只不过是个
You're just.
狗屁
another asshole.
我们都会死在这里
And we're both gonna die down here.
嗯，你就是未来，好吧
Yeah, you're the future, all right.
所有试图和北美联系的努力都失败了
All attempts to contact the North American facility continue to fail.
中断多久了？
How long have they been off the air?
17个小时
Seventeen hours.
他们可能失踪了 但是我们的计划保持不变
We must consider them lost. But our plans remain unchanged.
所有的数据都会传到这个设备上
All data will be transferred to this facility.
研究会在我个人的监督下继续
and the research will continue under my personal supervision.
我希望一个月之内能出结果
I expect results within one month.
先生们，你们不会等太久的
You won't have to wait that long, boys.
因为我马上就会来找你们
Because I'm coming for you.
还有
And.
我还会带一些朋友一起来
I'm gonna be bringing a few of my friends.
你只不过是个
You're just.
狗屁
another asshole.